preferred411.com 2015-03-23

# P411 - Escort Screening and Verification Service

Preferred411 has created this privacy statement to declare its commitment to the privacy of its customers and users of this website. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Preferred411 uses, maintains and discloses information collected from its customers and users of its websites. We take your privacy very seriously, and recognize the importance of maintaining your privacy as the cornerstone of our business' success. 

Information We Collect

* * *

When you sign up for a membership, Preferred411 may require your personal information, such as: name, e-mail address, telephone numbers, and website URLs. If your private information has been collected, it will be deleted and destroyed once the verification process has been completed, with the exception of your email address and client id. 

Preferred411 may also collect information about how users access the website using a tracking ID unique to each user through the use of cookies. This information is for internal use only and does not personally identify you in any way. 

How We Use This Information

* * *

Your client id is required for you to be able to log in and use Preferred411. Your email address will be used to receive renewal reminders and important service related correspondence. If you do not wish to provide us with a working email address or do not wish to receive communications from us via email, please do not signup. 

Information on our site is only collected by us and no one else. Preferred411 will not in any way share this information with a third party either for free or by selling it, unless required by law in our jurisdiction. 

Disclosure of Information

* * *

We use various credit card processing companies to accept payments for our services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes. 

Security Policy for Transmission of Payment Card Details

* * *

For credit card transactions, your information is secured by using 128 bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology, which encrypts information you input. 

In fact, the entire Preferred411 site is secured by using 128 bit SSL technology, to encrypt your what information there is on the site. 

Membership Renewals

* * *

We do not automatically renew any membership, and there is no need to cancel your membership to ensure you will not be charged again. When your membership is about to expire, you will receive email notifications and can decide if, and how, you wish to pay to renew your membership. 

Refund Policy

* * *

We do not offer refunds. In the event of a disputed transaction, please contact support at [support@preferred411.com](mailto:support@preferred411.com). 

Other Websites

* * *

The Preferred411 website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Preferred411 is not responsible for the privacy practices of any other site. 

Your Responsibility

* * *

You are responsible for the security of your password. Make sure you keep it in a safe place and do not share it with others. Your client id should only be given out via Requests found on P411, this is for your own safety and security. Always remember to log out after your session ends to ensure that others cannot access your account. You should take this precaution not only if you are using a public computer, such as at a library or internet café, but even when using your private computer in your home. 

Changes to this Policy

* * *

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement.
